michaelpage.ae 2013-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Michael Page

**Data Protection and Privacy Policy**

Michael Page International's online service is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe and secure user experience.  We will ensure that the information you submit to us via our website at [www.michaelpage.ae](http://www.michaelpage.ae/) ("The Michael Page International Site") remains private, and is only used for the purposes set out in this policy. 

**The Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Your personal details, including your name, e-mail address and CV, are held and used by us for the following purposes:

  1. For matching your coded details with job vacancies, to assist us in finding you the position that most suits you; 
  2. For keeping you informed of Michael Page services, news and wider developments in your chosen field; 
  3. For tailoring the version of our website you see when you log on to make it relevant to you; and/or 
  4. For compiling salary and other surveys of our candidates.

 **Disclosures of your information**

We will share your information within the Michael Page International group of companies where necessary in order to provide you with our recruitment services. 

It is possible that Michael Page International could merge or be acquired by another business. If this happens, we may share the information that relates to you with the new owners of the business and their advisers. You will be sent notice of such an event.

Your CV and related information will be sent to prospective employers but only where you give your consent. Such employers may be located both inside and outside the United Arab Emirates.

We may also release information relating to you to regulatory or law enforcement authorities, if required to do so. We also reserve the right to disclose the information we have collected about you to our professional advisors and to other persons to the extent that Michael Page International contracts out any aspect of the operation of its recruitment agency services.  These third parties will be acting under similar undertakings of confidentiality as Michael Page International.

 **Job Alerts**

To subscribe to job alerts emails, you will be required to provide your e-mail address, which will be used for the purpose of keeping you informed, by e-mail, of the latest jobs in your nominated industry and/or industry news via job alerts.

 **Should you decide that you no longer wish to receive this information, unsubscribe links are provided in every job alert email that you receive.**

 **Curriculum vitae ("CV")**

We give you the option of submitting your CV via this website. You can do this either to apply for a specific advertised job or for consideration by our recruitment consultants for positions as they come up.  Although your CV will be stored online, it will only be accessible by Michael Page International group recruitment consultants, working both inside and outside the United Arab Emirates. Your CV will also be e-mailed directly to our recruitment consultants who review your details and enter them onto our central in-house database. This database, including the information relating to you, can be accessed by any of our recruitment consultants working in other offices of the Michael Page International group, both inside and outside the United Arab Emirates.

You can update your CV at any time, simply by following the same procedure to submit a new CV. Your old CV will automatically be replaced. 

**Aggregate Information about Michael Page International online visitors**

We gather information and statistics collectively about all visitors to this website and all of the Michael Page websites worldwide, for example, which area users access most frequently and which services users access the most. We only use such data in the aggregate form. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users and how we can continually improve our online services to create a better overall experience for our users.  We also publish some of this information on the Michael Page websites worldwide.

 **Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file which is sent from a web server to a web browser when that browser visits the server's site. Find out more about the use of cookies on [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "This link opens in a new window.") Cookies are used on the [www.michaelpage.ae](http://www.michaelpage.ae/) website to remember your login, to track web traffic on an aggregate basis so that no individuals are identified, to keep session information such as your last search (this information is disposed of every time you close your web browser). Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this, please look at the help menu on your browser. However, switching off cookies will restrict your use of our website.  

 **Access**

You have the right at any time to ask us for a copy of the information supplied by you that we hold. We have the right to charge an administrative fee for this service. If you would like to make a request for information, please contact [dpa@michaelpage.ae](mailto:dpa@michaelpage.ae) You also have the right to ask Michael Page International to stop using your information.

 **Other websites**

Please note that clicking on to links and banner advertisements may result in your transferral to another website, where data privacy practices may be different to that of Michael Page International. Visitors should consult the other websites' privacy policies as we are not responsible for, and have no control over, information that is submitted to or collected by these third parties. 

**Internet-based transfers**

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this web site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy may be changed by Michael Page International at any time. If we change our privacy policy in the future, we will set out those changes here, so that you will always know what personal information we gather, the purposes we might use it for and to whom we might disclose it.  
If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about Michael Page International's online privacy commitment, please feel free to e-mail us at [dpa@michaelpage.ae](mailto:dpa@michaelpage.ae) or call your local office to speak to one of our representatives.

 **Equal Opportunities**

Michael Page International is an equal opportunities employer and a company committed to diversity.  This means that all job applicants and members of staff will receive equal treatment and that we will not discriminate on grounds of gender, marital status, race, ethnic origin, colour, nationality, national origin, disability, sexual orientation, religion or age. 

As part of our commitment to equal opportunities we may from time to time use information provided by you for the purposes of diversity monitoring. Any such information will be used on an anonymised basis in accordance with the terms of our Privacy Policy.
